Huth, Geoffrey A.; Papers mss137
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Publications, 1965-1966; 1969-2006; 12; 30.75 cubic ft.
  - Paper Publications, 1965-1966; 1969; 1972-2006; 12.1; 28.5 cubic ft.
    - Score, Joel, Recently we analyzed, ca. 1988 (Box 16 (S-Sq) (12-Publications), Folder 35)
    - Score, Joel, untitled, 1987 (Box 16 (S-Sq) (12-Publications), Folder 36)
    - Scott, Jordan, From blert, above/ground broadside #242, 2005 (Box 16 (S-Sq) (12-Publications), Folder 37)
    - Scrap, advertising ephemera, 1989- (Box 16 (S-Sq) (12-Publications), Folder 38)
    - Scrap, #'s1-6, 1986- (Box 16 (S-Sq) (12-Publications), Folder 39)
    - Scraplet 5.5, 1988 (Box 16 (S-Sq) (12-Publications), Folder 40)
    - The Scrivener, 1977-1978 (Box 16 (S-Sq) (12-Publications), Folder 41)
    - The Scrivener, 1977-1978 (Box 16 (S-Sq) (12-Publications), Folder 42)
    - The Scrivener, 1979 (Box 16 (S-Sq) (12-Publications), Folder 43)
    - The Scrivener, 1980 (Box 16 (S-Sq) (12-Publications), Folder 44)
    - The Scrivener, 1981 (Box 16 (S-Sq) (12-Publications), Folder 45)
    - The Scrivener, 1982 (Box 16 (S-Sq) (12-Publications), Folder 46)
    - Seattle Small Press Poetry Review, 1994 (Box 16 (S-Sq) (12-Publications), Folder 47)
    - Seattle Small Press Poetry Review, 1994 June (Box 16 (S-Sq) (12-Publications), Folder 48)
    - The Seer in the Weird, Undated (Box 16 (S-Sq) (12-Publications), Folder 49)
    - Selby, Spencer, Malleable Cast, 1995 (Box 16 (S-Sq) (12-Publications), Folder 50)
    - Semantics Could Vanish, Fluxonyms, 1989 (Box 16 (S-Sq) (12-Publications), Folder 51)
    - Semantics Could Vanish, And, Miekal; Was, Liz, Fluxonyms, 1989 (Box 16 (S-Sq) (12-Publications), Folder 52)
    - Shaw-Young, Jordan, 2 U's, ca. 1987 (Box 16 (S-Sq) (12-Publications), Folder 53)
    - Shikatani, Gerry, Q Tangent 4, 1991 (Box 16 (S-Sq) (12-Publications), Folder 54)
    - Shiki Haiku Calendar 2003, Undated (Box 16 (S-Sq) (12-Publications), Folder 55)
    - Shippy, Peter Jay, Pursued by Silhouettes, 1992 (Box 16 (S-Sq) (12-Publications), Folder 56)
    - Shit Diary 11, 1994 (Box 16 (S-Sq) (12-Publications), Folder 57)
    - Shively, Bill, 2nd edition, 1989 (Box 16 (S-Sq) (12-Publications), Folder 58)
    - Shively, Bill, sleep by the river waiting/sleep in the shade of stone, 1986 (Box 16 (S-Sq) (12-Publications), Folder 59)
    - Shredding +.........., #'s1, 1988 (Box 16 (S-Sq) (12-Publications), Folder 60)
    - Sh'WIPE! a-2, 1987-1988 (Box 16 (S-Sq) (12-Publications), Folder 61)
    - Sick Roof, #'s 1, 3-4, 1989 (Box 16 (S-Sq) (12-Publications), Folder 62)
    - Skelley, Jack, God Raised My Dummy, ca. 1992 (Box 16 (S-Sq) (12-Publications), Folder 63)
    - Skemer, Arnold, C, inscribed by author, 1992 (Box 16 (S-Sq) (12-Publications), Folder 64)
    - Skemer, Arnold, D, signed with long inscription, 1995 (Box 16 (S-Sq) (12-Publications), Folder 65)
    - Skemer, Arnold, Investigations of the Cyberneticist, signed and inscribed, 1999 (Box 16 (S-Sq) (12-Publications), Folder 66)
    - Skemer, Arnold, Momus, signed and inscribed, 1999 (Box 16 (S-Sq) (12-Publications), Folder 67)
    - Skemer, Arnold, Ruins of the City, signed and inscribed, Undated (Box 16 (S-Sq) (12-Publications), Folder 68)
    - Sky Views, June 1984, January 1985, Volume 3, #'s1-5, 1988/1989 (Box 16 (S-Sq) (12-Publications), Folder 69)
    - Sky Views, Volume 3, #'s4/5, 1988 (Box 16 (S-Sq) (12-Publications), Folder 70)
    - Slacks, Burphy, Jr., Smoke Whittles plantain, 1990 (Box 16 (S-Sq) (12-Publications), Folder 71)
    - Sleeping Fish, O, 2004 (Box 16 (S-Sq) (12-Publications), Folder 72)
    - Sleeping Fish, #0.5, 2004 (Box 16 (S-Sq) (12-Publications), Folder 73)
    - The Sleeze Art News, Undated (Box 16 (S-Sq) (12-Publications), Folder 74)
    - Sloan, DeVillo, Ourang-Outang, 1986 (Box 16 (S-Sq) (12-Publications), Folder 75)
    - Smear, 1988 (Box 16 (S-Sq) (12-Publications), Folder 76)
    - Smile Magazine, ca. 1989 (Box 16 (S-Sq) (12-Publications), Folder 77)
    - Smith, Dale, My Vote Counts, 2004 (Box 16 (S-Sq) (12-Publications), Folder 78)
    - Smith, Mimi, "Hot/Cold", 1976; 2003 (Box 16 (S-Sq) (12-Publications), Folder 79)
    - Smith, Mimi, "On/Off", 2003 (Box 16 (S-Sq) (12-Publications), Folder 80)
    - Snyder, Marc and Luc, Fierens, Postfluxpostbooklet #61, 2003 (Box 16 (S-Sq) (12-Publications), Folder 81)
    - Sollfrey, Stacey, Feeling the Roof of a Mouth That Hangs Open, 1991 (Box 16 (S-Sq) (12-Publications), Folder 82)
    - Sollfrey, Stacey, Turning Sights in a Circular Driveway, 1989 (Box 16 (S-Sq) (12-Publications), Folder 83)
    - Sonnefeld, Mark & Andrew Topel, Chemical, 2003 (Box 16 (S-Sq) (12-Publications), Folder 84)
    - Source, 1990 (Box 16 (S-Sq) (12-Publications), Folder 85)
    - The South Carolina Review, Volume 20, #2, Jonathan Brannen poem, 1988 (Box 16 (S-Sq) (12-Publications), Folder 86)
    - Spatola, Adriano, zeroglyphics, 1977 (Box 16 (S-Sq) (12-Publications), Folder 87)
    - Spence, Pete, Chaosmos, 2005 (Box 16 (S-Sq) (12-Publications), Folder 88)
    - Spidertangle: The Book, a coincidental miscellany of now vispo, 2002 (Box 16 (S-Sq) (12-Publications), Folder 89)
    - Spiel, c a, Spiel's shat.ter.tan.gle.shred, 2001 (Box 16 (S-Sq) (12-Publications), Folder 90)
    - Spillane, Mickey, I, the Jury, abridged for the modern reader, ca. 1988 (Box 16 (S-Sq) (12-Publications), Folder 91)
    - The Splendor of the Word, New York Public Library, 2005 October 21-2006 February 12 (Box 16 (S-Sq) (12-Publications), Folder 92)
    - Spoliation Results, #9, 11, 13-14, 2002 (Box 16 (S-Sq) (12-Publications), Folder 93)
    - Sponge Studio, advertising postcards, 1990 (Box 16 (S-Sq) (12-Publications), Folder 94)
    - Spore 2.0, 2005 (Box 16 (S-Sq) (12-Publications), Folder 95)
    - Spun, #62, review of dbqp and includes SJRC #38, 1990 (Box 16 (S-Sq) (12-Publications), Folder 96)
    - SQReview #1, 1994 (Box 16 (S-Sq) (12-Publications), Folder 97)
    - Squinting Towards the Dim Star, The Annual Litmag Anthology of Writing, design by Geof Huth, lacking the light blue cover, 2002 (Box 16 (S-Sq) (12-Publications), Folder 98)
    - Starkey, David, A Year with Gayle, And Others, 1993 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 1)
    - Starkey, David, A Year with Gayle, And Others, 1993 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 2)
    - Steinmetz Poems and Stories, an anthology of Student Writing, Steinmetz Middle School, 1990 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 3)
    - Steinmetz Poems and Stories, an anthology of Student Writing, Steinmetz Middle School, 1991 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 4)
    - Steinmetz Poems and Stories, Spring 1989, design by Geof Huth, Undated (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 5)
    - Steinmetz Poems and Stories, Winter 1989, design by Geof Huth, Undated (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 6)
    - Steinmetz Poems and Stories, Spring 1992, design by Geof Huth, Undated (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 7)
    - Stetser, Carol, signed and inscribed, 2004 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 8)
    - Stetser, Carol, Copy-Book, 2003 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 9)
    - Stetser, Carol, Mappaemundi, 2006 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 10)
    - Stetser, Carol, Serenade, 2005 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 11)
    - Sticks, #2, 1994 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 12)
    - Sticks, #4, Include poems published by dbqp, 1998 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 13)
    - Lo Straniero, #'s 11&13, 1991-1992 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 14)
    - Stained paper archive, #a, 1993 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 15)
    - Stahl, Enno, 2 Reisen, Nachts, 1990 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 16)
    - Stengl, Bruce, Of a Feather, 1986 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 17)
    - Stickey, J., untitled, 1989 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 18)
    - A Straynge Catalogue, mention 3 versions, 1989 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 19)
    - A Straynge Catalogue, advertising postcard, 1989 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 20)
    - Strike/Strike 1990-1993, Undated (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 21)
    - Su Car, Volume 10, #26, 2002 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 22)
    - Sub Bild, #'s2-3, poems by G. Huth, featuring work from ADM, 1990- (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 23)
    - Subterranean Monuments: Burckhardt, Johnson, Hujar, June 30-September 17, 2006 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 24)
    - Suder, Thomas & a.j. weigon: The Vera Strange Tapes, Undated (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 25)
    - Sudol, Diane, Keeping Guard, 1989 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 26)
    - Suel, Lucien; Bennett, John M.; Nikonova, Rea, AM, ca. 1995 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 27)
    - SUFFOCATION OF THE MOTHER, hysteria, # 1/2, 1989 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 28)
    - Sughe, Jnifr, She has bones, 1986 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 29)
    - Suncoast Amateur, #13, review of dbqp, 1991 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 30)
    - Support Your Local Poet, ca. 1988 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 31)
    - Swallow, Festival of Plagiarism, Glasgow, Scotland, 1989 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 32)
    - 1988 Swampbook, Undated (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 33)
    - Swamp Press, advertisement flyers, Undated (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 34)
    - Swede, George, Bifids, 1984 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 35)
    - Swede, George, condom, 1986 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 36)
    - Swede, George, from the bridge, 1986 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 37)
    - Swede, George, 10, 1983 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 38)
    - Swede, George, Shamelessly, 1987 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 39)
    - Swede, George, thick mist, 1986 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 40)
    - Swede, George, windo, 1982 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 41)
    - s'WIPE, 1988 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 42)
    - Synergism: An Anthology of Collaborative Writing, 1995 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 43)
    - Syracuse Poems and Stories, 1983; 1985 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 44)
    - Syzygy, #1, 1990 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 45)
    - taboo jadoo, #'s2-8, 1990-1994 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 46)
    - Talarico, Andrea Jade, Spinning with the Tornado, 2003 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 47)
    - A Talk by Marvin Sackner, Announcement, 1990 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 48)
    - Tand, #44, 1990 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 49)
    - Tanerai gasta asibiaru, #'s1-6, 1993 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 50)
    - Tanerai gasta asibiaru, #'s1-5, 1994 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 51)
    - Taproot, #'s9/10, 14, 1988- (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 52)
    - Taproot, #'s17/18, Undated (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 53)
    - Taproot Reviews, #'s1-4, 1992-1994 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 54)
    - Taproot Reviews, #'s5, 9/10, Reviews of dbqp, especially #7/8 page 23, 1994-1996 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 55)
    - Taylor, Thomas Lowe, Photo Images, 2005 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 56)
    - Teet, Volume 25, #11, 1990 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 57)
    - Temporary Culture, #5-7, 1991-1992 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 58)
    - tentatively, a convenience, Plenial Wer, 1990 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 59)
    - tentatively, a convenience, pedicab, 1995 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 60)
    - tentatively, a convenience, Telepathy Receptive Training, 1991 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 61)
    - Tentativity, 1988 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 62)
    - Teraz Mowie, #11-15, 1991-1992 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 63)
    - Teraz Mowie, #16, 1993 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 64)
    - Thirteen Poetry Magazine, Volume VII, #3, 1989 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 65)
    - This is Important, #'s1-15, 1980-1988 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 66)
    - This is not art, 1990 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 67)
    - Three Dimensional Broadside, #1, 1991 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 68)
    - Through the Finger-Printed Glass, An Anthology of Student Writing, Mont Pleasant Middle School, design by Geof Huth, Fingerprints are Geof Huth's, 1998 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 69)
    - Tierney, Allen & rbarnes, (lone) Vernon, Selection from Fin D, 1991 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 70)
    - Tightrope, #10, 14, 1980; 1989 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 71)
    - Time Worm, #11, 1987 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 72)
    - Tin Wreath, #'s1-16, 1985-1987 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 73)
    - Tin Wreath, #'s17-27, 1990-1992 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 74)
    - the tiny, #1, with poorly printed visual poems, 2005 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 75)
    - Tomoyasu, Larry, Close, Cover, 1993 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 76)
    - Tomoyasu, Larry, mockingbird/litmus, 1990 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 77)
    - Tomoyasu, Larry, Radio Electronics, 1993 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 78)
    - Tomoyasu, Larry, Starkweather, 1991 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 79)
    - Topel, Andrew, Assassin, inscribed to Geof Huth, 2004 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 80)
    - Topel, Andrew; Altemus Reed, Avant Hybrids: A Collaboration, 2003 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 81)
    - Topel, Andrew, as Anna KorYntz, Axle, 2004 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 82)
    - Topel, Andrew, using name Anna KorYntz, The Brief Autobiography of Anna KorYntz, 2005 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 83)
    - Topel, Andrew, (c)lone, inscribed to Geof Huth, 2004 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 84)
    - Topel, Andrew, Crevice, 2002 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 85)
    - Topel, Andrew, Encyclopoetica, 2002 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 86)
    - Topel, Andrew, EU mahnt strenge Klima-Regeln an, 2004? (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 87)
    - Topel, Andrew, Feet Teeth, inscribed to Geof Huth, 2003 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 88)
    - Topel, Andrew, foreigner, 2004 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 89)
    - Topel, Andrew, Genesis, inscribed to Geof Huth, 2004 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 90)
    - Topel, Andrew, Indictment, 2004 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 91)
    - Topel, Andrew & John M. Bennett, Loot, 2004 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 92)
    - Topel, Andrew, midnight, inscribed to Geof Huth, 2004 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 93)
    - Topel, Andrew, mystiFICATION, 2003 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 94)
    - Topel, Andrew, Notes, inscribed to Geof Huth, 2004 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 95)
    - Topel, Andrew, Numericans, 2005 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 96)
    - Topel, Andrew & John Bennett, numero dos, 2004 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 97)
    - Topel, Andrew, Pain Tings, signed and inscribed, 2004 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 98)
    - Topel, Andrew, as John Cese, Plato's Republic Revisited, 2004 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 99)
    - Topel, Andrew, Poetic Events You Can Try at Home, 2004? (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 100)
    - Topel, Andrew & Luc Fierens, Postfluxpostbooklet #59, 2003 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 101)
    - Topel, Andrew, Puzzles, 2004 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 102)
    - Topel, Andrew, Red Assassin, 2002 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 103)
    - Topel, Andrew, Red Lines, inscribed to Geof Huth, 2004 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 104)
    - Topel, Andrew, re-echoes, 2003 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 105)
    - Topel, Andrew & Steve Dalachinsky, Reverse World, trance-forms/transformed, Collaborative Visuals, 2004 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 106)
    - Topel, Andrew & Bennett, John M., Singularity, 2005 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 107)
    - Topel, Andrew, Skew, inscribed to Geof Huth, 2004? (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 108)
    - Topel, Andrew, Skull pulse, 2005 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 109)
    - Topel, Andrew, Spheres, 2004? (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 110)
    - Topel, Andrew, T4 Hood, 2004 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 111)
    - Topel, Andrew, Threads, 2002 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 112)
    - Topel, Andrew and Thomas Lowe Taylor, untitled, 2002 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 113)
    - Topel, Andrew, visualinguals, 2004 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 114)
    - Topel, Andrew, Vogue, 2004 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 115)
    - Topel, Andrew, windows, 2004? (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 116)
    - Topel, Andrew, X, 2002 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 117)
    - Townsend, Cheryl A.; and Paul Weinman, "Cat" and White Boy Up a Tree, 1991 (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 118)
    - Towler, Matt, postcards, 1988- (Box 17 (St-To) (12-Publications), Folder 119)
    - Trammell, Robert, Jack Ruby and the Origins of the Avant-Garde in Dallas, 1986 (Box 18 (Tr-Ve) (12-Publications), Folder 1)
    - Transfer, #6, 1991 (Box 18 (Tr-Ve) (12-Publications), Folder 2)
    - Transmog, #1-19, 1991-1995 (Box 18 (Tr-Ve) (12-Publications), Folder 3)
    - travischaney; azalea out of vanadium sky, 1994 (Box 18 (Tr-Ve) (12-Publications), Folder 4)
    - travis, b; Bennett, John M., sending, 1995 (Box 18 (Tr-Ve) (12-Publications), Folder 5)
    - Tray Full of Lab Mice Publications, 1989 (Box 18 (Tr-Ve) (12-Publications), Folder 6)
    - Troendle, Yves, Sophie, 1987 (Box 18 (Tr-Ve) (12-Publications), Folder 7)
    - Truly Fine, ca. 1985; 1989 Spring; 1990 Spring (Box 18 (Tr-Ve) (12-Publications), Folder 8)
    - Tundra, 2, 2001 (Box 18 (Tr-Ve) (12-Publications), Folder 9)
    - Turbulence #1, 1993 (Box 18 (Tr-Ve) (12-Publications), Folder 10)
    - Tuyau, #'s 60, 69-70, 73, 78-80, 116, 118, 120-121, 124-125, 129-130, 135, 141-143, 1987 (Box 18 (Tr-Ve) (12-Publications), Folder 11)
    - Twenty Years of British Art from the Sackner Archive of Concrete and Visual Poetry, 1988 (Box 18 (Tr-Ve) (12-Publications), Folder 12)
    - Two-Ton Santa, #'s14-15, 21, 24, 28, 32-33, 35, 37, 38-40, 52-61, 1989 (Box 18 (Tr-Ve) (12-Publications), Folder 13)
    - Typewriter, #'s4-6, 1973-1975 (Box 18 (Tr-Ve) (12-Publications), Folder 14)
    - Typewriter, #'s7-10, 1976; 1978; 1980 (Box 18 (Tr-Ve) (12-Publications), Folder 15)
    - Typografiprosjekt, Visningsrommet USF, 13-20 oktober 2005, accompanied Audiatur: Katalog for NY Poesi (Box 18 (Tr-Ve) (12-Publications), Folder 16)
    - U-Direct, Conference Issue, 1994 (Box 18 (Tr-Ve) (12-Publications), Folder 17)
    - Umbrella, Volume II, #1, review of wreadings, 1988 (Box 18 (Tr-Ve) (12-Publications), Folder 18)
    - Unarmed #36, from Reed Altemus, September 2004, 2002 (Box 18 (Tr-Ve) (12-Publications), Folder 19)
    - under-know-ledge, ca. 1984 (Box 18 (Tr-Ve) (12-Publications), Folder 20)
    - Underwhich Editions, Catalogues, 1985-1987 (Box 18 (Tr-Ve) (12-Publications), Folder 21)
    - Union Shop Bluff, #2, 1991 (Box 18 (Tr-Ve) (12-Publications), Folder 22)
    - Unknown Worlds, Undated (Box 18 (Tr-Ve) (12-Publications), Folder 23)
    - Up a Creek, 1991 (Box 18 (Tr-Ve) (12-Publications), Folder 24)
    - UPPER LIMIT MUSIC, #'s1-5, 1992-1994 (Box 18 (Tr-Ve) (12-Publications), Folder 25)
    - UU, David, candle, postcard, 1991 (Box 18 (Tr-Ve) (12-Publications), Folder 26)
    - UU, David, candle, leaflet, 1991 (Box 18 (Tr-Ve) (12-Publications), Folder 27)
    - UU, David, Poet's Lament, 1983 (Box 18 (Tr-Ve) (12-Publications), Folder 28)
    - UU, David, Poet's Lament, 2nd edition, 1991 (Box 18 (Tr-Ve) (12-Publications), Folder 29)
    - UU, David, Transfiguration, in memory of bpNichol, 1990 (Box 18 (Tr-Ve) (12-Publications), Folder 30)
    - La Vache Bigaree, one of 40 copies, ca. 1990 (Box 18 (Tr-Ve) (12-Publications), Folder 31)
    - van, 1, 93-126, 130, 139-141, 2002-2003 (Box 18 (Tr-Ve) (12-Publications), Folder 32)
    - van #142, 2005 (Box 18 (Tr-Ve) (12-Publications), Folder 33)
    - Van Sebroeck, Annina, & Luc Fierens, Rencontre, signed by artists, 2005 (Box 18 (Tr-Ve) (12-Publications), Folder 34)
    - The Vanderbilt Poetry Review, 1972-1976 (Box 18 (Tr-Ve) (12-Publications), Folder 35)
    - The Vanderbilt Poetry Review,1981-1982, Undated (Box 18 (Tr-Ve) (12-Publications), Folder 36)
    - The Vanderbilt Poetry Review, 1978-1983 (Box 18 (Tr-Ve) (12-Publications), Folder 37)
    - The Vanderbilt Photography Review, 1981-1982 (Box 18 (Tr-Ve) (12-Publications), Folder 38)
    - Valoch, Jiri, poem for bpNichol, 1988 (Box 18 (Tr-Ve) (12-Publications), Folder 39)
    - Vallely, Jim, "We know you're in", 1990 (Box 18 (Tr-Ve) (12-Publications), Folder 40)
    - The Valley Fever, Volume 6.1, ca. 1987 (Box 18 (Tr-Ve) (12-Publications), Folder 41)
    - Vassilakis, Nico, architexts, 2003 (Box 18 (Tr-Ve) (12-Publications), Folder 42)
    - Vassilakis, Nico, artaud what, 1993 (Box 18 (Tr-Ve) (12-Publications), Folder 43)
    - Vassilakis, Nico, artaud what, 1993 (Box 18 (Tr-Ve) (12-Publications), Folder 44)
    - Vassilakis, Nico, Bus, 1989 (Box 18 (Tr-Ve) (12-Publications), Folder 45)
    - Vassilakis, Nico, Bus, 1989 (Box 18 (Tr-Ve) (12-Publications), Folder 46)
    - Vassilakis, Nico, The Colander, 2002 (Box 18 (Tr-Ve) (12-Publications), Folder 47)
    - Vassilakis, Nico, Diesel Hand, Undated (Box 18 (Tr-Ve) (12-Publications), Folder 48)
    - Vassilakis, Nico, distortdissolve, 2004 (Box 18 (Tr-Ve) (12-Publications), Folder 49)
    - Vassilakis, Nico, Dornobber, 1989 (Box 18 (Tr-Ve) (12-Publications), Folder 50)
    - Vassilakis, Nico, Emma: The Sign of, Undated (Box 18 (Tr-Ve) (12-Publications), Folder 51)
    - Vassilakis, Nico; Topel, Andrew, here there, 2005 (Box 18 (Tr-Ve) (12-Publications), Folder 52)
    - Vassilakis, Nico, Kyoo, 1992 (Box 18 (Tr-Ve) (12-Publications), Folder 53)
    - Vassilakis, Nico, A Name for Radio, 1993 (Box 18 (Tr-Ve) (12-Publications), Folder 54)
    - Vassilakis, Nico, Sequence, Geof Huth mentioned in afterword, 1996 (Box 18 (Tr-Ve) (12-Publications), Folder 55)
    - Vassilakis, Nico, Sequence, Geof Huth mentioned in afterword, 1996 (Box 18 (Tr-Ve) (12-Publications), Folder 56)
    - Vassilakis, Nico, Space Bar Pencil, 2002 (Box 18 (Tr-Ve) (12-Publications), Folder 57)
    - Vassilakis, Nico, Species Pieces, 2005 (Box 18 (Tr-Ve) (12-Publications), Folder 58)
    - Vassilakis, Nico, stampOlogue, 2005 (Box 18 (Tr-Ve) (12-Publications), Folder 59)
    - Vassilakis, Nico, Texts for Nothing, but Cut Up, 2003 (Box 18 (Tr-Ve) (12-Publications), Folder 60)
    - Vassilakis, Nico, An Unusual Sacrifice, 1993 (Box 18 (Tr-Ve) (12-Publications), Folder 61)
    - Vassilakis, Nico, A Very Brief History of Visual Poems, Part two: Early Twentieth Century, Undated (Box 18 (Tr-Ve) (12-Publications), Folder 62)
    - A Vast Slur of Lipstick, An Anthology of Student Writing, design by Geof Huth, 2003 (Box 18 (Tr-Ve) (12-Publications), Folder 63)
    - Vautier, Ben, Total Art Matchbook, 1982 (Box 18 (Tr-Ve) (12-Publications), Folder 64)
    - Velocity, #'s1-2, 1985 (Box 18 (Tr-Ve) (12-Publications), Folder 65)
    - Velocity, #'s3-4, 1985 (Box 18 (Tr-Ve) (12-Publications), Folder 66)
    - Velocity, #'s5-6, 1986 (Box 18 (Tr-Ve) (12-Publications), Folder 67)
    - Velocity, #'s7-8, 1986-1987 (Box 18 (Tr-Ve) (12-Publications), Folder 68)